onhercam.tv 2011-05-27

# OnHerCam Privacy Policy - Internet Privacy and Safe Surfing

OnHerCam.com is committed to maintaining a privacy policy that benefits each individual customer's preferences.

NOTE: Our privacy policy is null and void in cases of fraud!

This policy explains the privacy practices for Leescliffe Limited, a UK-based corporation, (hereinafter referred to as "Leescliffe Limited", "OnHerCam", "site", "our", "we", or "us"). In order to provide interactive computer billing and fraud services, Leescliffe Limited collects and uses certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, what we use and how you can interact with Massive Online in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect and use.

1) Information Collection:  
Visitors can access our Web site home page and browse our Web site without disclosing any personal data. However, in order to provide you with a particular product or service online, Massive Online may request that you voluntarily supply Leescliffe Limited with primary personal data (such as name and email address) and identifiers (such as credit card number and web site password). Leescliffe Limited gives you the option of using a secure transmission method of sending such information.

Leescliffe Limited does not store or record financial information. Credit and banking information is not recorded by Leescliffe Limited systems.

Leescliffe Limited receives and stores all information that you enter in our Web site and billing pages. In addition, Leescliffe Limited collects information about you during your visit, such as your IP Address, and Leescliffe Limited employs its software in order to ascertain your physical location when making a purchase. However, we do not collect information from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. You are required to provide Leescliffe Limited with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide Leescliffe Limited with such information could result in voiding your Agreement with Leescliffe Limited.

You can inquire about your personal data by sending an e-mail to fraud@onhercam.com. Within a week, Leescliffe Limited shall provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which Leescliffe Limited keeps about you. Leescliffe Limited charges a $25 processing fee for the request. Prior to completing your request, Leescliffe Limited may require that you provide Leescliffe Limited with proof of your identity. Leescliffe Limited reserves the right to refuse any request for information though Leescliffe Limited will communicate the reason for its decision.

2) Information Use:  
Leescliffe Limited is the sole owner of the information collected on its sites. Leescliffe Limited will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed it this policy. Leescliffe Limited shall release data when required by law, to enforce its Agreement or the contract rights of its clients. Leescliffe Limited shares the following data with the owner/operator of the web site from which you are purchasing goods and services utilizing Leescliffe Limited services: the URL you are purchasing goods or services from, your e-mail address, your name, your address, your phone number, your date of birth, and your agreement to be bound by Leescliffe Limited terms and conditions. Leescliffe Limited uses the data it collects for the technical administration of the Web site, research and development, and fraud deterrence.

3) Information sharing:  
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to governmental institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

4) Email correspondence:  
Leescliffe Limited may request a confirmation when you receive and open and e-mail communication delivered by Leescliffe Limited. We archive and identify the origination IP address of all email sent into our network.

5) Third party information:  
Occasionally, Leescliffe Limited receives information from third parties to compare it to information that you had provided to Leescliffe Limited for fraud prevention purposes.

6) Cookies:  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Leescliffe Limited employs "cookie" technology. We use Cookie to store personal data, to authenticate you as a Site user, for security purposes, and to track our affiliate click-throughs and sign-up rate.

7) Children:  
Leescliffe Limited does not request, or knowingly collect, personal data from anyone under the age of 18. Furthermore, Leescliffe Limited does not knowingly give children the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves on our web site.

8) Security:  
We take every precaution to protect our visitors' information. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction, or accidental loss. Leescliffe Limited utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. Leescliffe Limited encrypts the information that you provided.

In addition, Leescliffe Limited does everything to protect your information off-line. All employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with, the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. Leescliffe Limited employs a username and password scheme in order to limit and achieve access to our computer network by our employees and third parties.

9) Correction/Updating Personal Information:  
You may access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, updating, and in some instances deleting from our system any information deemed inaccurate. You may request to access your information by sending a request to:

Administrator  
Consumer Protection Dept.  
Leescliffe Limited  
Fort House, Old Hartley,  
NE26 4RL Whitley Bay,  
Tyne & Wear,  
United Kingdom  
or e-mail: ohc@onhercam.com.

If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at the above address.

(Revised November 2, 2009)
